Chaos Ritual vs.
Toon Turbo.
Game 1.
Toon Turbo goes first.
Toon Turbo sets Crossout Designator, then sets Dominus Spark, then sets Infinite Impermanence.
Draw for turn.
Chaos Ritual sets Mind Shuffle, then activates Ragged Records of Rites to reveal a Ritual Spell
and search a monster that names it.
Toon Turbo chains Ash Blossom & Joyous Spring in response to negate Ragged Records's Deck effect.
Ragged Records's effect is negated.
Chaos Ritual Normal Summons Magician's Rod.
Chaos Ritual activates the Rod.
Toon Turbo chains Infinite Impermanence in response.
the Rod's effect is negated.
Chaos Ritual activates Black Chaos.
Toon Turbo chains Dominus Spark in response, then banishes the Rod.
Chaos Ritual places the Trap face-up from the Deck.
Chaos Ritual activates the Trap, then adds Skull Archfiend of Chaos from the Deck, then discards Skull Archfiend.
Chaos Ritual activates Skull Archfiend, then sends Light and Darkness Ritual from the Deck to the
Graveyard, then adds Magician of Dark Chaos - Black Chaos from the Deck.
Chaos Ritual returns Magician of Dark Chaos to the Deck, then Special Summons Black Chaos.
Chaos Ritual activates Skull Archfiend, then returns the Ritual to the Deck, then returns Black Chaos
to the Deck.
Chaos Ritual returns the Rod to the Deck, then Special Summons Skull Archfiend.
Chaos Ritual banishes Black Chaos, then Special Summons Dark Magician of Destruction.
Chaos Ritual activates the Magician, then adds The Gaze of Timaeus from the Deck.
Chaos Ritual activates Timaeus.
Toon Turbo chains Crossout Designator in response, then banishes Timaeus from the Deck.
Timaeus's effect is negated.
Chaos Ritual sets The Fallen & The Virtuous.
Chaos Ritual's the Magician attacks directly for 2800 damage.
Chaos Ritual's Skull Archfiend attacks directly for 2500 damage.
Draw for turn.
Chaos Ritual activates the Trap, then adds Skull Archfiend from the Deck, then discards Skull Archfiend.
Chaos Ritual activates Skull Archfiend, then sends the Ritual from the Deck to the Graveyard, then
adds Magician of Dark Chaos from the Deck.
Toon Turbo Normal Summons Funny Dark Rabbit.
Chaos Ritual flips Fallen & Virtuous face-up in faceup.
Chaos Ritual activates Fallen & Virtuous, then sends Albion the Branded Dragon from the Extra Deck
to the Graveyard.
Fallen & Virtuous destroys Funny Dark Rabbit.
During the End Phase, Chaos Ritual activates Albion the Branded Dragon.
Chaos Ritual sets Fallen & Virtuous.
Draw for turn.
Chaos Ritual activates the Trap, then adds Black Chaos from the Deck, then discards the Rod.
Chaos Ritual's the Magician attacks directly for 2800 damage.
Chaos Ritual wins the duel.
Chaos Ritual wins Game 1.
Chaos Ritual vs.
Toon Turbo.
Game 2.
Toon Turbo goes first.
Toon Turbo sets Infinite Impermanence, then Normal Summons Funny Dark Rabbit.
Toon Turbo activates Funny Dark Rabbit, then adds Toon World the Perfect World from the Deck.
Toon Turbo activates World the Perfect World.
Toon Turbo activates World the Perfect World, then adds Toon Bookmark from the Deck.
Draw for turn.
Chaos Ritual activates Griffoh, then banishes Funny Dark Rabbit, then sets Mind Shuffle.
Chaos Ritual puts Funny Dark Rabbit on the field.
Chaos Ritual activates the Trap to search a monster that mentions Light and Darkness Ritual, then
discard a card.
Toon Turbo chains Ash Blossom & Joyous Spring in response to negate the Trap's Deck effect.
the Trap's effect is negated.
Chaos Ritual activates Ragged Records of Rites, then adds Black Luster Soldier - Soldier of Light
and Darkness from the Deck.
Chaos Ritual returns Black Luster Soldier to the Deck, then Special Summons Black Chaos, then sends
Black Chaos to the Graveyard.
Chaos Ritual sets Skull Archfiend of Chaos.
Chaos Ritual activates Black Chaos, then places the Trap face-up from the Deck.
Draw for turn.
Chaos Ritual activates the Trap, then banishes Funny Dark Rabbit, then adds Skull Archfiend from the Deck.
Chaos Ritual discards Skull Archfiend, then puts Funny Dark Rabbit on the field.
Chaos Ritual activates Skull Archfiend, then sends the Ritual from the Deck to the Graveyard, then
adds Magician of Dark Chaos - Black Chaos from the Deck.
Toon Turbo activates Funny Dark Rabbit, then adds World the Perfect World from the Deck.
Toon Turbo activates Bookmark, then adds Comic Cat from the Deck.
Toon Turbo activates World the Perfect World.
Toon Turbo activates World the Perfect World, then adds Comic Cat from the Deck.
Toon Turbo Normal Summons Comic Cat.
Draw for turn.
Chaos Ritual activates the Trap, then banishes Funny Dark Rabbit, then adds Black Chaos from the Deck.
Chaos Ritual discards Black Chaos, then puts Funny Dark Rabbit on the field.
Chaos Ritual activates Ragged Records, then banishes Comic Cat, then adds Black Luster Soldier from the Deck.
Chaos Ritual puts Comic Cat on the field.
Chaos Ritual activates Skull Archfiend.
Toon Turbo chains Ghost Belle & Haunted Mansion in response.
Skull Archfiend's effect is negated.
Chaos Ritual activates the Ritual, then recovers the Ritual from the Graveyard, then recovers Black Chaos
from the Graveyard.
Chaos Ritual returns Black Luster Soldier to the Deck, then Special Summons Black Chaos.
Toon Turbo activates Comic Cat.
Chaos Ritual activates the Trap to search a monster that mentions the Ritual, then discard a
card, then returns Black Chaos to the hand, then Ritual Summons Magician of Dark Chaos.
Chaos Ritual activates Magician of Dark Chaos.
Toon Turbo chains Infinite Impermanence in response.
Chaos Ritual activates the Trap to search a monster that mentions the Ritual, then discard a
card, then returns Magician of Dark Chaos to the hand, then Special Summons Black Chaos.
Chaos Ritual recovers Ragged Records from the Graveyard.
Chaos Ritual activates Black Chaos, then banishes Comic Cat, then banishes Funny Dark Rabbit.
Chaos Ritual activates the Ritual, then banishes Griffoh, then Ritual Summons Magician of Dark Chaos.
Chaos Ritual Flip Summons Skull Archfiend.
Chaos Ritual's Black Chaos attacks directly for 3000 damage.
Chaos Ritual's Magician of Dark Chaos attacks directly for 2800 damage.
Chaos Ritual's Skull Archfiend attacks directly for 2500 damage.
Chaos Ritual wins the duel.
Chaos Ritual wins Game 2.
Final score: Chaos Ritual 2–0.